Thrasher mss., 1938-2006 LMC 2560
Lilly Library
Thrasher mss.
1938-2006
Lilly Library
Saulet, Robert
LMC 2560
1 Box 1 standard
The Thrasher mss. consists predominantly of letters and cards received by Jane Thrasher from Robert Saulet, ca. 1938-1953, with four letters from or written on behalf of Charlton Heston, 2004-2006.
Access Restrictions
This collection is open for research.
Many collections are housed offsite; retrieval requires advance notice. Please make an appointment a minimum of one week in advance of your visit.
Acquisition Information
Gift: 2007
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in chronological order.
Biographical Note
Jane Thrasher (1921-2009) was a resident of Bloomington, Indiana who correspondended with Robert Saulet and actor Charlton Heston. Thrasher was a partner of her family's Bloomington business, Thrasher Hardware Company.
Scope and Content Note
The Thrasher mss. consists predominantly of letters and cards received by Jane Thrasher from Robert Saulet, ca. 1938-1953, with four letters from or written on behalf of Charlton Heston, 2004-2006.
Heston, Charlton; Saulet, Robert; Thrasher, Jane
- Correspondence
  - 1930 (Box 1)
  - 1937 (Box 1)
  - 1938 (Box 1)
  - 1939 (Box 1)
  - 1940 (Box 1)
  - 1941 (Box 1)
  - 1942 (Box 1)
  - 1944 (Box 1)
  - 1945 (Box 1)
  - 1950-1955 (Box 1)
  - Charlton Heston, 2004-2007 (Box 1)